(Leonard:)No, seriously,
I think
(Leonard:)I've finally figured out
my problem with women.
(Sheldon:)The capybara is the largest
member of the rodent family.
(Leonard:)What does that have to do
with me and women?
(Sheldon:)Nothing.
It was a desperate attempt
(Sheldon:)to introduce an alternate topic
of conversation.
(Leonard:)My problem is,
I don't project confidence.
(Leonard:)So I decided that
the next time I meet a woman
(Leonard:)I think is attractive,
rather than holding back
(Leonard:)and being cautious,
I'm going to assume
(Leonard:)the mantle of self-assurance.
(Raj:)Oh, yeah?
What's that look like?
(Leonard:)Hi.
(Leonard:)I'm Leonard.
(Leonard:)And you are beautiful.
(Leonard:)You pop, sparkle
and buzz electric.
(Leonard:)I'm going to pick you up
at 8:00,
(Leonard:)show you a night
you will never forget.
(Raj:)Where are we going?
(Howard:)Good news.
(Howard:)I made it
onto the team
for the new Defense Department